http://www.augustamed.com/privacy

Skip to main content
COVID-19 & Flu: Get the latest information
MenuSearch form Search
About UsMaps & DirectionsMyAugusta ChartPay Your BillCareersVolunteeringContact UsServicesFind a ProviderPatients & VisitorsAdvance DirectiveBusiness OfficeCheer CardsFood on CampusGift ShopHealth Exchange Resource GuideMedical RecordsNurse & Caregiver RecognitionPatient RelationsSpiritual CareVisiting InformationCommunity OutreachAbout UsAMI Farm at Augusta HealthCommunity Event Screening RequestCommunity Health Needs AssessmentFaith Community NursingScholarship ProgramSpeakers' Bureau RequestStrategic FundingMake a GiftAbout UsMake an ImpactGrateful Patient StoriesWays to GiveGiving SocietiesSpecial EventsYou are hereHome / AboutIn this SectionAbout UsAugusta Medical GroupAwards & RecognitionBoard of Directors & Committee MembersLeadershipMission, Vision & ValuesNews RoomNews ReleasesEvent CalendarHealth Focused BlogHealth Matters MagazineContact Augusta Health(540) 332-4000(800) 932-0262 Toll FreeLocation78 Medical Center DriveFishersville, VA 22939Mailing AddressPO Box 1000Fishersville, VA 22939Website PrivacyAugusta Health is dedicated to serving the health care needs of the community, and we are committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our website.The information contained on this website is for informational purposes only. It is neither intended nor implied to be a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified healthcare provider before starting any new treatment or with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this website.Information Automatically CollectedWhen you visit our site or mobile app, your web browser automatically sends us non-personal information such as: IP addresses, time and date of your visit, type of browser software, the internet domain (such as your service provider) through which you access the internet, and the internet address of the site from which you linked to our site. We use this information to help us maintain this site, by determining the number of visitors to different sections of our site, to ensure the site is working properly, and to help us make our site more accessible and useful.We will not use this information to identify individuals. We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you provide such information.Other Information We CollectOur site uses forms to collect messages or to request certain services. When you provide personal information, we will only use it for the purpose stated. We do not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information to third parties for non-Augusta Health use.External LinksThis site contains links to a variety of other sites. Augusta Health is not responsible for the privacy practices or information provided on those sites.Comment PolicyWhile we encourage you to follow Augusta Health on our social media sites, use good judgment when commenting. Please review our Comment Policy.CookiesWe may use cookies to customize this site for visitors. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies. You are not required to accept any cookies to use this site. Additionally, we use third-party tools which may install cookies.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google Analytics uses a first-party cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user when you visit this site. They also use third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our site. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You may opt-out of Google Analytics. Review Google Analytics' Terms of Service and Google's Privacy Policy for more information.FacebookFacebook provides tools, such as pixels that allow us to track visits to our website through ads and to create custom audiences of people who have visited our website. We use this information to provide insight about the effectiveness of our ads and to target ads more appropriately. You can opt-out of the collection and use of this information through the Digital Advertising Alliance's consumer choice page.Questions?If you have any questions about this page or the website in general, you may contact Marketing.(540) 332-4000(800) 932-0262Contact Us78 Medical Center Dr, Fishersville, VA 22939FacebookTwitterInstagramLinkedInYouTubeNewsletter SignupHealth Focused BlogNewsEventsHealth Matters Magazinefor Employeesfor PhysiciansSecure LoginWebmailRecipient of the US World & News Reports Best Regional Hospital and Healthgrades 50 Best Hospitals award. View our Awards & RecognitionCopyright © 2020 Augusta Health. All Rights Reserved.Website PrivacyComment PolicyNondiscrimination and Accessibility PolicyPatient PrivacySite MapTranslate this page
